Guide to the Calhoun College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2016 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student records for the Classes of 2003 to 2016, Accession 2018-A-0078
  - Class of 2010
    - Muller, Benjamin, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Nagalla, Bhaktapriya, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Netter, Gabriela, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Nguyen-Phuc, Alyssa, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - O'Neil, Quincy, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - O'Shaughnessy, Kathryn, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Park, Ji Ho, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Phillips, D. Streeter, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Quam, Justin, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Reed, Theresa, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Renfield-Miller, Charlotte, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Rice, Daniel, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Riley, John, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Robinson, Thomas, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Rodriguez, Mercedes, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Rodriques, Adam, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Roggenbuck, Christopher, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Rowe, Juliann, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Scheiner, Michael, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Schneider, Kurt, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Schnoor, Mary, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Shields, Matthew, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Siegl, Benjamin, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Silva, Stephen, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Sirianni, Antonio, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Snyder, Scott, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Steinman, Susan, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Stephens, Kevin, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Stevens, Ford, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Sukhdev, Mahima, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Swan, Anna, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Sykes, Naima, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Tekeste, Genet, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Townsend, Daniel, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Tung, Margaret, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Turbow, Sarah, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Tykocinski, David, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Uhrich, Ross, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Waldman, Kate, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Wallace, Jack, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Walsh, Erin, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Wassung, Alissa Lauren, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Weiser, Julia, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - White, Matthew, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Williams, Neely, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Wilton, Brandon, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Wixted, Mary, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Yang, Alina, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Young, Brian, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Yudofsky, Emily, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Yurkiewicz, Ilana, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Zaragoza, Laura, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Zhou, Han, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Class of 2011
    - Adeniyi, Bashir, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Al Dakkak, Nafez Mazen, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Alexander, Colin Darcy, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Atura, Ann Bendersky, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Baldwin-Hunter, Ashley Lauren, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Bannon, Shane John, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Barnett, Caroline Robbins, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Berman, Kate Beryl, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Brink, Joseph Benjamin, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Brooks, Skyler Dune, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Cahill, Christopher, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Carpenter, Hayley Anne, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Cheng, John Tachung, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Claunch, Kristin Lian, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Coster, Luciano Evaristo, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Davis, Gwynedd Lleyn, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - DeFilippis, Ersilia Marie, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Dyba, Jasmine Patricia, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Edwards, Sarah Elizabeth, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Ellner, Samantha Grace, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Esquival, Joshua Peter, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Falcone, Johnathan Daniel, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Faller, Avery Wagner, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Fehling, Kara Binder, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Feng, Jerry, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Fidali, Brian Christopher, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Finley, Robert Cory, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Glasser, Nathaniel Joseph, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gonzales, Katherine, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gordon, Veronica, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Gustafson, Kelsey Jean, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Haddad, George Monsour, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Han, Bing, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Harris-Kaye, Laurika Pearl, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Hayes-Larson, Eleanor Louise, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Hernandez, Ricardo Rolando, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Howard, Hyatt Marcel, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Howell, Emily Claire, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hudy, Endre, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ing, Kevin Jon, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Jacoby, Cody, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Khan, Murad Mustafa, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kim, Jeonghyun, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Kong, Alice Mi Jung, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Koury, Jake Taylor, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Kozyryev, Ivan, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Kridsada, Kim, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - La, Dung Quoc, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Lee, Joseph, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Lee, Matthew S., 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Leveille, Kenneth John, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Li, Linda Yijia, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Light, David, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Liggins, James Lawrence, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Long, Meredith Glenn, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Lundeen, James Pollard, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Mahmoud, Tariq Magdy, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Mason, Brenden James, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Maurer, Lydia Rose, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - McCollum, Matthew Allen, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - McDermott, Katherine A., 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Mesham, David Robert, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Morgan, Rachel A., 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Mulligan, Frances Hayden, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Mulvihill, Zachary Francis, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Norton, Jessica Ashley, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Nsababera, Olive Umuhire, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Nunziato, Carl Anthony, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Olson, Eric Reed, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Omrani, Sepeedeh Sahar, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Okemgbo, Kaetochi Chiebere, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Patton, Agusta Leigh, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Perry-Coon, Christopher William, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Petrelli, Stefana, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Radding, Amy Johanna, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Roberts, Nia Louise, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Romine, Natalie Lauren, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Russ, Rebecca Megan, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Saffold, Christine Elena, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Salomon, Sarah, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Sarin, Natasha R., 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Schwartz, Mandi, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Seeam, Dharam Gupt, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Seidman, Gabriel Evan, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Selem, Sarah Marie, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Shapiro, Sophia Rose, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Siegel, Daniel Joseph, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Sloan, Sarah Hartman, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Sohn, Andrea Jeeyon, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Sri-Kumar, Nikila Susheela, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Stein, Alexandra Happ, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Stempel, Adam Lindbeck, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Subramanyam, Pritha, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Sutter, William Maxwell, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Swiswa, Batsirai Neville, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Timberlake, Andrew Thomas, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Van Dyck, James, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Waldemore, Marissa Lee, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Wallace, Marcus A., 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Weiss-Goldman, Naomi Esther, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Wolff, John Edward, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Wu, Melissa Siping, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Wu, Tianchi, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Zhang, Joanne Yula, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Zhao, Xingmeng, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Zhou, Quingan, 2007-2011 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Class of 2012
    - Addison, Alexandra L., 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Ahmed, Rahma Sheikh, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Anderson, William Benton, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Bockius-Suwyn, Zoe Emelie, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Bogado, Laura, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Brown, Andrew Louis, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Brown, Kathryn, 2008-2012 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Calhoun, Ava Margaret, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Cantor-Stone, Joshua Gabriel, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Carlsmith, Joseph Keller, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Casasanto, Nicolas Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Cashen, Michelle Lynne, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Chang, Ya, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Cheng, Tony, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cheung, Zoe Beatrice, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cho, Chris Moonho, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Chonkov, Nikola Atanasov, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Chmelar, Mark William, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Cigarroa, Barbara Carisa, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Crawford, Conor Remo, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Darnell, Alicia Marie, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Delgado, Eric Nelson, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - DiBrell, Mollie Ann, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Dowd, Ryan Dart, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Droge, Abigail Marie, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Engle, Courtney, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Evans, Joshua D., 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Fischer, Jennifer Marie, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Gabriel, Paul Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Gallogly, Katharine S., 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Gottesdiener, Matthew Ross, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Greenberg, Margaret Jasper, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Gregoire-Wright, Taylor Albert, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Gutierrez, Gabriela Luz, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Hashimoto, Hayden Wong, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Helfaer, Samuel Joshua, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Hendler, Micah, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Henly, Claire Emma, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Ho, Kevin, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Holbrook, Jonathan Lazar, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Jenn, Gabrielle Morgan, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Jiminez, Elibet Soledad, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Jiminez, Nadia, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Kamdar, Aditya Vijay, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Kao, Erica, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Krumholz, Rebecca Rose, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Kraszewski, Andrew Paul, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Lee, James, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Lewis-McNeil, Lillian Rannells, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Litman, Zachary Charles, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Liu, Jillian Claire, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Locarno, Chelsea Jayne, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - LoPresti, Christopher Clark, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Love, DeJuan Edward, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Ludwig, Patrick Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Magarik, Yasha Avram, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Marichal, Ana, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - McMullen, Karoline Evan, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - McCrary, Jacob Austin, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Miller, Kyle Parker, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Morse, Robert Edson, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Neal, Noah Robin, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Neil, Charles Lyndon, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Nunn, Abigail Elizabeth, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Pagan, Khalid Wesley, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Pan, Lisa April, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Pickett-Bortko, Emmanuelle Laine, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Plana, Alejandro G., 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Rallis, Dean, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Reddy, Ashna Dodla, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Reveiz, Kenneth, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Rose, Bradley Jason, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Rosett, Max Roth, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Roth, Katelyn Marie, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Russotto, Rick Daniel, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Saiyed, Ana, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Sanders, Samantha Blair, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Serrao, Julian, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Shethji, Pooja Pankaj, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Stasinopaulos, Georgios, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Steinbrook, Daniel Edward, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Tekin, Etkin, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Torchon, Tasha Fausta, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Tsang, Amy Huilin, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Veltfort, Sophia Elena Pies, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Vesuna, Sam Sarosh, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wallach, Marc Ulysses, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Wang, Wendy Liu, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Weissler, Elizabeth Hope, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Wesley Stuart, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Wilczynski, Peter Vincent, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Worthy, Sable Alexandria, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Yagoda, Maria Louise, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Ziegler, Chad N., 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Zucker, Michael Benjamin, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2013
    - Anderberg, Emily Irene, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Balian, Moses Jonah, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Benzimra, Nathaniel S., 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Berman, Marjorie Allison, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Bilinski, Alyssa Marie, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Bird, Isabel Munroe, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Blackburn, Dean, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Bogart, Devorah Leah, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Bruner, Raisa Pearl, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Budovitch, Max Missner, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Burston, Alexandra Emma, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Callahan, Erin Moore, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Chen, Gang, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Cuenca, Karen, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Meredith Morgan, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Dodd, Richard Watkin, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Dolan, Patrick Sherman, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Drimal, Chloe Alexa, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Enamandram, Sheila Sree, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Evelyn, Jacob Morris, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Fayette, Alexandra E., 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Fernandez, Rafael Jesus, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Fishkis, Rachel Beth, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Kay, Adelaide A., 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Gillman, Farris Jean, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Giuffrida, Michael Peter, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Glodo, Rachel M., 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Goddu, Mariel Kathryn, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Gutierrez, Alejandro, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Guzick, Sarah Crim, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Harvey, Kristopher L., 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Hastie, Jordan Alexandra, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Hayes, Mollie Michelle, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Hoffer-Hawlik, Matthew Jonathan, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Holmes, Charles, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Ivanov, Natalie Stoyanova, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Jackson, Brandon Scott, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Jackson-Gibson, Adele, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Jaffe, Adela Ariel, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Jaffe, Caroline Adair, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Jaffer, Sana Fatema, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Jang, Brian Han, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Jang, Eileen Kao, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Johri, Shweta, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Kawash, Mitchel Eli, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Khare, Divya, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Laporte-Oshiro, Catherine, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Lee, Christina, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Leu, Andrew, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Litman, Anna Marie, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Liu, Danquing, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Lovett, Jared Anders, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Malcolm, Jeffrey Russell Kyle, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Mangwendeza, Yemurai Adda, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Martinez, Claudia, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Mathy, Lauren Destree, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Morgan, Lauren Diaz, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, John Philip, 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Morse, Elliot Coleman, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Muncey, Meghan Elizabeth, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Nadelmann, Jennifer Beth, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Nakajima Nozomi, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Nakata, Nicole Noriko-Marie, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Namkung, Fun Ju, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Nwigwe, Christian Ebere, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Okeefe, Patrick Regis, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Oppenheimer, Jessica, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Papillion, Natalie Olivia, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Park, Isaac, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Pease, Alison Maura, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Platzer, Laura, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Polinger, Charles Michael, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Pollock, Ryan Francis, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Prasad, Vinay A., 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Revesz, John William, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Savit, Chelsea Lea, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Schmidt, Marian Lennart, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Schumacher, Whitney Adrienne, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Shah, Smith, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Sherman, Benjamin Marc, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Shimer, Eliot Prosser, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Skilton, Amalia Elizabeth, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Stanley-Becker, Thomas Galerntner, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Starr, Elizabeth Houghton, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Uno, Meghan Elizabeth, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Urosa, Erik Alejandro, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Villalobos, Jairo, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Walker, Jordan Trishton, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Wang, Nicholas C., 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Weigel, Melissa K., 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Weltmer, Jeremy Tomlinson, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Wohl, Shirlee, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Woo, Seung Hyun, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Yi, Annie, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Young, Chase Jennings, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Yu, Lewan, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Zhang, Baobao, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Zhao, Zixiang, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Zhuang, Jasmine Billyen, 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Class of 2014
    - Addison, Kathleen, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Antoszyk, Matthew, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Bakal, Zachary, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Barry, Sarah, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Benoit, Laura, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Bertez, Conrad, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Billings, Ryder, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Blanson, Nina, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Boateng, Kwabena, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Boynton, Li, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Buck, George, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Coa, Mona, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Carlsen, Gregory, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Carter, Terrell, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Chen, Tin Lee, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Chiang, Stephanie, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Chin-Loy, Terrence, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Clavadetscher, Kerry Lynn, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Cohen, Peter, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Conery, Mitchell, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Crouch, Martina, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Cunetta, Michael, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Davis, John, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Donnelley, Claire, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Ett, Rachel, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Fritzberg, Suzanna, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - Gallogly, Grace, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Garza, Natalia, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Goldstein, David Zrubavel, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - Guertler, Charlotte, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Han, Paul, 2010-2014 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - Harvey, Daniel Jacob, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hay, Vivienne C., 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hendler, Reuben Abraham, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Heng, Vibol, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Henry, Elizabeth, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Henry, Madeline, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Hollander, Kevin, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Houlihan, Molly, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Hunter, Jacob, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Hutzler, Kyle, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Isper, Alexander, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Jeffrey, Juliann, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Jernaill, Jasmeet, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Kannan, Shibi, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Karetsky, Ethan, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Kejsefman, Uriel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Kim, Gene, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Kirshenbaum, Ariel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Kits van Heyningen, Hendrik, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Klebanoff, Emily, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Klement, John, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Kotak, Dhawal, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Krasulova, Katarina, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Latterner, Leah, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Lee, Brian, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Lee, John, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Lee, Samantha, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Lekkas, Filippos, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Leunen, Michael, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Levine, Nathalie, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, Victoria Beth, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Li, Yidan, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Lindberg, Dana, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Liu, Chang, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Locke, Charlotte, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Lounsbury, Connor, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 36)